http://www.cpperformance.com/t-privacy.aspx

Login
Your Account
Contact Us
Shopping Cart (0)
Technical and Product Advice Blog
See us on:
Is your boat in the gallery?Image Gallery
Instructions & Guides:Instructions
Find Parts by Mercury Model:OEM Part Finder
What's popular today?Popular Items
What are you looking for Today?
Need Help? Call Us:
Corsa Performance
Custom Marine (CMI)
Your Privacy
CP Performance is committed to protecting your privacy. We only use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide support and upgrades for our products. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
How does CP Performance protect customer information?
We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure server layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the interenet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
What about "cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We do not use cookies to collect or store any information about visitors or customers.
Will CP Performance disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
CP Performance does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. CP Performance may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information.
CP Performance may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of CP Performance, our users, or others.
In Summary
CP Performance is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at cpperformance.com as simple as possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Your Consent
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by CP Performance, Inc. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
CP Performance also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibliity of the linked site and CP Performance has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. CP Performance cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.
